So you're not a cultist?
إذن أنت لست من أتباع الطائفة؟
You're not planning to become a saint, right?
أنت لا تخطط لأن تصبح قديسًا، أليس كذلك؟
Do you like garlic?
هل تحب الثوم؟
Do you have good eyesight?
هل لديك نظر جيد؟
Joowon can't eat ginger and garlic.
جووون لا يستطيع أكل الزنجبيل والثوم.
They're delicious, though.
إنهم لذيذون، رغم ذلك.
Is anyone in there?
هل يوجد أحد هناك؟
Is this what you wanted to do?
هل هذا ما أردت فعله؟
I guess you really didn't want to take the photo.
أعتقد أنك لم ترغب حقًا في التقاط الصورة.
There are lasers coming out of your eyes.
هناك أشعة الليزر تخرج من عينيك.
That camera is weird.
هذه الكاميرا غريبة.
I've got to keep it.
لا بد لي من الاحتفاظ به.
I think you need to be honest.
أعتقد أنك بحاجة إلى أن تكون صادقا.
I'm always honest.
أنا صادقة دائما.
Though I always feel like I'm the one losing,
على الرغم من أنني أشعر دائمًا أنني الخاسر،
it's okay.
لا بأس.
Because I'm bad at hiding my emotions.
لأنني سيئة في إخفاء مشاعري.
You're not afraid of me finding out
أنت لست خائفا من أن أكتشف ذلك
but of getting hurt.
ولكن من التعرض للأذى.
But...
لكن...
even so, I still like you.
مع ذلك، لا أزال أحبك.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Joowon hyung?
جووون هيونغ؟
I missed you, Dongha.
لقد افتقدتك، دونغها.
It's so cold today. Is that all you came in?
الجو بارد جدًا اليوم. هل هذا كل ما جئت به؟
I was in a hurry.
لقد كنت في عجلة من أمري.
The journey was longer than I thought.
وكانت الرحلة أطول مما كنت أعتقد.
What were you thinking on your way back here?
ماذا كنت تفكر فيه في طريق عودتك إلى هنا؟
That a bunch of vampires are living in the center of the city.
أن مجموعة من مصاصي الدماء يعيشون في وسط المدينة.
I thought about exposing them.
فكرت في فضحهم.
Just kidding.
أنا فقط أمزح.
Tsk.
شكرًا لك.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You said you can't sleep on the floor.
قلت أنك لا تستطيع النوم على الأرض.
I'll sleep here.
سأنام هنا.
I'm not used to you being so nice to me.
أنا لست معتادًا على أن تكون لطيفًا معي بهذه الطريقة.
Let's just sleep together.
دعونا ننام معًا.
What?
ماذا؟
It's not like it's the first time.
إنها ليست المرة الأولى.
When was this?
متى كان هذا؟
My birthday party.
حفل عيد ميلادي.
Why do you look like you were going to cry?
لماذا تبدو وكأنك على وشك البكاء؟
There weren't kids around my age
لم يكن هناك أطفال في مثل عمري
and those who attended were old people.
وكان الحاضرون من كبار السن.
I see.
أرى.
I cried a lot when I was that young too.
لقد بكيت كثيرًا أيضًا عندما كنت صغيرًا.
Why?
لماذا؟
Because I didn't want to drink blood.
لأنني لم أرغب في شرب الدم.
I didn't know I was a vampire.
لم أكن أعلم أنني مصاص دماء.
Is that... possible?
هل هذا... ممكن؟
When Godfather found me,
عندما وجدني العراب،
I was very sick.
لقد كنت مريضا جدا.
To save me, he turned me into a vampire.
لإنقاذي، حولني إلى مصاص دماء.
Oh...
أوه...
Oh.
أوه.
That day,
في ذلك اليوم،
I was afraid your wound might be poisoned,
كنت خائفة من أن يكون جرحك مسموما،
so I wanted to remove the poison—
لذلك أردت إزالة السم
Hyung. Are you tired now?
هيونغ، هل أنت متعب الآن؟
No. Why?
لا. لماذا؟
When I was a kid,
عندما كنت طفلا،
I loved lying down here to look at the sky.
لقد أحببت الاستلقاء هنا للنظر إلى السماء.
What is that star?
ما هو هذا النجم؟
It's not like living in the countryside makes me a professor of constellations.
إن العيش في الريف لا يجعلني أستاذًا في الأبراج الفلكية.
I don't even know if it's a star or space trash.
أنا لا أعرف حتى إذا كان نجمًا أم قمامة فضائية.
But, so what?
ولكن ماذا في ذلك؟
It's pretty. That's all that matters.
إنه جميل. هذا كل ما يهم.
Pretty.
جميل.
Oh. How did you find that...
أوه. كيف وجدت ذلك...
It found its owner.
وجدت صاحبها.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
We don't react well to silver.
نحن لا نتفاعل بشكل جيد مع الفضة.
Then take it off.
ثم أخلعها.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Why would you keep wearing it?
لماذا تستمر في ارتدائه؟
I said I'm fine.
قلت أنني بخير.
No, give it to me.
لا، أعطني إياه.
I like you, Dongha.
انا معجب بك، دونغها.
To be honest,
صراحة،
I regretted leaving like that on that day.
لقد ندمت على مغادرتي في ذلك اليوم بهذه الطريقة.
I liked you so much.
لقد اعجبتني كثيرا.
But I'm afraid
ولكنني خائف
you might get hurt because of me.
ربما تتأذى بسببي.
I wanted to be honest with you as you said.
أردت أن أكون صادقا معك كما قلت.
That's why I came to look for you after plucking up my courage.
لهذا السبب جئت للبحث عنك بعد أن جمعت شجاعتي.
Why aren't you saying anything?
لماذا لا تقول شيئا؟
That's my answer.
هذا جوابي.
Let's go home together.
دعونا نذهب إلى المنزل معًا.
Everyone says they miss you.
الجميع يقولون أنهم يفتقدونك.
Can I go back?
هل يمكنني العودة؟
Of course. That's our home.
بالطبع. هذا منزلنا.
Did you come back alone?
هل عدت وحدك؟
What's with that reaction?
ما الأمر مع هذا التفاعل؟
Well... I mean...
حسنا... أعني...
I guess I had my hopes up for nothing.
أعتقد أنني كنت أعلق آمالي على لا شيء.
Hopes up for what?
الآمال معلقة على ماذا؟
Could it be me?
هل يمكن أن أكون أنا؟
Hey, Dongha!
مهلا، دونغها!
I missed you.
أفتقدك.
Dongha, I missed you!
دونغها، لقد افتقدتك!
Why are you so thin?
لماذا أنت نحيف جداً؟
Didn't you miss us?
ألم تفتقدنا؟
We've been waiting for you.
لقد كنا في انتظارك.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
[Rental Agreement]
[اتفاقية الإيجار]
Please take care of me.
من فضلك اعتني بي.
That aside.
هذا جانبا.
Let's respect each other's privacy—
دعونا نحترم خصوصية بعضنا البعض
Again? What's with that privacy thing again?
مرة أخرى؟ ما الأمر مع مسألة الخصوصية هذه مرة أخرى؟
Is secretly being a vampire your privacy?
هل كونك مصاص دماء سريًا يعتبر خصوصية لك؟
No, I'm not talking about you.
لا، أنا لا أتحدث عنك.
I'm talking about you guys.
انا اتحدث عنكم يا رفاق.
If I catch you.
إذا أمسكتك.
Hyung.
هيونغ.
We're not that terrible.
نحن لسنا سيئين لهذه الدرجة.
Right, right.
يمينًا، يمينًا.
I'll take good care of Dongha.
سأعتني بـ دونغها جيدًا.
Hey! Stay away from him! Shoo!
هي! ابتعد عنه! شو!
You guys look so happy.
أنتم تبدوون سعداء جدًا.
Everyone!
الجميع!
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
-Thank you!
-شكرا لك!
Wow... This is it.
واو...هذا هو.
I want to cry.
أريد أن أبكي.
Hey.
يا.
Is this why you called me back?
هل هذا هو السبب الذي جعلك تتصل بي مرة أخرى؟
Hey, saying that would make us sad.
مهلا، قول ذلك سيجعلنا حزينين.
If you like it, we'll buy you three meals a day.
إذا أعجبك ذلك، فسنشتري لك ثلاث وجبات يوميًا.
Never mind...
لا تهتم...
Let's go play basketball after eating.
دعنا نذهب للعب كرة السلة بعد الأكل.
No.
لا.
Gyumin hates playing basketball.
غيومين يكره لعب كرة السلة.
Doesn't he hate it 'cause he's bad at it?
ألا يكره ذلك لأنه سيء ​​فيه؟
That's right. Sports and him don't get along well.
صحيح. الرياضة معه لا تتوافقان جيدًا.
What are you talking about? I'm better than humans.
عن ماذا تتحدث؟ أنا أفضل من البشر.
Hey. As a human, I don't like what you just said.
مهلا. كإنسان، لا يعجبني ما قلته للتو.
Shall we bet?
هل نراهن؟
Okay! Come along!
حسناً! تعال معنا!
Cha Eunho, you're on my team, right?
تشا أون هو، أنت في فريقي، أليس كذلك؟
Hey, how can you do that?
مهلا، كيف يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك؟
That's a foul.
هذا خطأ.
Hey, Han Dongha.
مرحبًا هان دونغها.
What about me?
ماذا عني؟
Eunho, I'm probably better than Gyumin.
أون هو، أنا ربما أفضل من غيومين.
What are you talking about? He's really bad.
عن ماذا تتحدث؟ إنه سيء ​​جدًا.
I've seen it.
لقد رأيته.
I'm speechless.
أنا بلا كلام.
You're really going to do the bet?
هل حقا سوف تفعل الرهان؟
Yeah.
نعم.
You have to be on my team, no matter what.
يجب عليك أن تكون في فريقي، مهما كان الأمر.
I'll always be on your team.
سوف أكون دائما في فريقك.
It's hot.
الطقس حار.
By the way...
بالمناسبة...
what did you mean that day?
ماذا تقصد في ذلك اليوم؟
What?
ماذا؟
You said, "Why would I..."
لقد قلت "لماذا أفعل ذلك..."
What about that?
ماذا عن ذلك؟
I mean...
أعني...
Could it be,
هل يمكن أن يكون؟
Why would I like someone like you?
لماذا أحب شخص مثلك؟
Something like that?
شيء من هذا القبيل؟
Are you crazy?
هل انت مجنون؟
Then what is it?
ثم ما هو؟
I don't know. Stop asking.
لا أعلم. توقف عن السؤال.
I need time to think about it.
أحتاج إلى وقت للتفكير في هذا الأمر.
Then let's check it.
إذن دعونا نتحقق من ذلك.
What?
ماذا؟
Let's...
دعونا...
check
يفحص
what that meant.
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
[Hanguk University]
[جامعة هانكوك]
Is it interesting?
هل هو مثير للاهتمام؟
Mmhmm.
ممممم.
What about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
Hyung, this is the library.
هيونغ، هذه هي المكتبة.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
Seriously.
بجد.
Do you like me that much?
هل تحبني لهذه الدرجة؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Since when did you start liking me?
منذ متى بدأت تحبني؟
Hmm... Right from the beginning.
مممم...منذ البداية.
Somehow I was pulled to you.
بطريقة ما، تم سحبي إليك.
If I don't see you,
إذا لم أراك،
I'd somehow be looking for you.
سأبحث عنك بطريقة ما.
[Yusin]
[يوسين]
[Park Dongjoo]
[بارك دونغجو]
[Lee Taehyung]
[لي تايهيونغ]
[Lee Dongyeol]
[لي دونغيول]
[Lee Juyoung]
[لي جويونغ]